<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

<channel>
<title>montti</title>
<description>montti's blog</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<link>https://montti.github.io/rss.xml</link>
<atom:link href="https://montti.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

<item>
<title>Deus Ex: Mankind Divided</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/deus-ex:-mankind-divided.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>I like games that give me tools and let me decide how to use them. Games with emergent, interconnected systems that reward exploration and experimentation. Games that blend the static and scripted with the systemic and emergent such that the world feels reactive and alive with possibilities. Games where everything you do is a choice.</p>
<p>Deux Ex games take these mechanics and intertwine them with narratives of espionage and global conspiracy, filled with major and minor characters with diverse motivations, goals and loyalties, and leave you free to find your own place and role in their world.</p>
<p>Mankind Divided is the most successful game at doing all of that since the original Deus Ex.</p>
<!--more-->
<p>Human Revolution, until the final catastrophe, presented a world full of hope for the bourgeoning possibilities of augmentation and self-directed evolution. Inequality was present but treated as a fixable problem by the game’s more thinky characters. The general spirit was one of optimism and of being on the brink of a new Renaissance — a period the game’s aesthetic design pillaged expertly.</p>
<p>Mankind Divided is a distinctly post-catastrophe world where Augs (augmented humans) are, due to distrust and fear (and the usual opportunism), treated very much as second-class citizens, if citizens at all — routinely brutalised by the police and other citizens, segregated and even shipped off to what are internment camps in all but name.</p>
<p>The Renaissance design influences are gone — no more ruffed collars, sadly — and replaced with a far more run-down, dirty aesthetic where environments feel quite brutalist with their rectilinear forms and big, chunky, square columns — reminiscent of the low poly, shiny-floored solidity of interiors in the original game. The architecture and urban spaces no longer speak of the hope of a bright future, now they dominate with austere oppressiveness.</p>
<p><a href="../images/mankind_divided_lights.jpg"><img src="../images/mankind_divided_lights.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>While the game’s chosen aesthetic is less inherently <em>pretty</em> than that of Human Revolution, the designers have done, if anything, an even better job of creating a beautiful, if stark, world. Even in some of the ugliest areas of the game — the Aug ghetto you visit, for example — the game’s environments are often stunning. Whether in the beautiful chaos of the tangled wires the world relies on for its information feeds or places where humans have tried to beautify their drab surroundings with light and colour, the game often stuns with its attention to the mise-en-scène.</p>
<p><a href="../images/mankind_divided_wires.jpg"><img src="../images/mankind_divided_wires.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>Mankind Divided tells a smaller story than any of the previous titles, focussing on a world very much going to shit. For people like me who love the original game this is <em>exciting</em>; we get to see the unfolding of events which will, eventually (hopefully in a later game), lead to Silhouette’s bombing of the Statue of Liberty and the founding of UNATCO. We also get to see big names we recognise from Deus Ex vying for position and orchestrating and reacting to events.</p>
<p>The game only has one hub — something which has been criticised but, to my mind, perfectly suits the purpose and character of the game. The enshittening of the world is told through the eyes of the city of Prague and its people. There are, of course, missions to other locations, but it’s Prague to which we keep returning and through which we witness rising tensions between Augs and ‘Naturals’ and the increasing hostility and, later, brutality of the police. Prague serves as focus and flashpoint for events of global significance. It’s a portrait of a world falling apart with Prague as the canvas.</p>
<p>The way XP is distributed has been rebalanced since Human Revolution which is a change for the better — it was the wrong way to be opinionated about player choices in a Deus Ex game. Weapons now seem less powerful, at least early on, which is a much better means of nudging players towards a more stealthy, less violent approach. Similarly, hacking tasks now reward more fairly based on goals rather than methods — you get XP regardless of whether you hacked a thing or found the code in the world. There are also <em>far</em> fewer unimportant computers to hack which is a blessing for those of us who find XP hard to ignore.</p>
<p><a href="../images/mankind_divided_mech.jpg"><img src="../images/mankind_divided_mech.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>Unfortunately, the hacking mini-game still exists. It’s a fine game in and of itself; just a very different activity to the rest of the game, which breaks immersion and the natural rhythm of fun infiltration action and exploration. It’s also irritatingly luck-based. The hacking in the original Deus Ex, which was just a progress bar, may not have been interactive, but waiting for the hacking bar to fill up created time pressure and tension without taking the player <em>out</em> of the game they were enjoying. It’s not a big deal, I just wish the devs had found a cleverer way to keep hacking active without breaking the game’s flow.</p>
<p>Level design is improved since Human Revolution with explorable spaces feeling simultaneously more natural and more labyrinthine. Finding alternate routes feels like a logical process rather than merely stumbling on Route B. Back doors <em>feel</em> like <em>back doors</em> rather than just… <em>other</em> doors, as they sometimes did in the previous game.</p>
<p>Infiltration is, of course, the meat of the game and the area where player choice has the most immediate impact. A stealthy, pacifistic run feels very different from an all-guns-blazing approach, which feels different again from taking everyone down without being seen. I took the latter approach during my first play-through, playing quite carefully and thoroughly, treating levels like real-time puzzle games as I worked out how to use my various tools to get <em>everyone</em> without ever being seen. I’m now playing new game plus mode (you keep your augmentations and gear) in a far more gung-ho fashion and it feels very different — the approach you take completely changes the function of the environments you’re navigating and thus how they feel as levels. Despite the thoroughness of my first play-through I’m finding plenty I missed including at least one major side-quest line.</p>
<p>A welcome change over Human Revolution is the return of having to choose between augmentations. Early in the game Adam discovers that alongside his regular, Sarif-supplied augmentations he seems to have a raft of super secret extra mega cool augmentations from a mystery source. Activating these augs, however, requires the de-activation of a regular augmentation, for at least some of the game. I wish that it were for all of the game — choice is key to Deus Ex and being forced to make difficult strategic choices between augmentations adds weight and tactical depth.</p>
<p><a href="../images/mankind_divided_stairs.jpg"><img src="../images/mankind_divided_stairs.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>Side-quests and main quests interweave more closely than they did in Human Revolution with core narrative content often being found in the side-missions. There’s also <em>far</em> more contextual narrative in the various books, magazines, newspapers, data pads and emails than in any of the previous games, much of it providing a tantalising look into the shaping of the J.C. Denton era world. For people who’ve played the original game there’s a wealth of rewarding reading in Mankind Divided.</p>
<p>Side-quest givers and other named NPCs now seem more situated in their place and circumstances. I really got a sense that these are people — from activists to police officers to Aug refugees and Naturals — each trying to survive in a world on the brink of collapse. Some give in to the anti-aug sentiment gleefully, others reluctantly. Some resist, others give up. Some try to profit from the misery while others attempt to cling to their morality. The array of reactions each feel real, personal and specific to that person’s circumstances and story and reflect the changes they see in the world around them as time passes in the game (spoiler: shit gets worse).</p>
<p><a href="../images/mankind_divided_lights.jpg"><img src="../images/mankind_divided_lights.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>While it still has the bombastic conspiracy stuff we know and love Deus Ex for, Mankind Divided finds a space in its world to tell very human stories that I found quite affecting.</p>
<p>Side-quests are as diverse as the people giving them — work for a mob boss, find a serial killer, help a couple of refugees acquire fake documents, reacquaint with old artificial friends — and all help tell the story of a world undergoing profound change and the people trying to cope with that change. More successfully than in any other Deus Ex game, you get to see the <em>effects</em> of the world-shaking events within which Jensen is enmeshed.</p>
<p>While a smaller, more focussed story than its predecessor, Mankind Divided is a <em>big</em> game. My first (careful) play-through took 60 hours and I’m already deep into my second. The focus on Prague allows the game to illustrate the changes happening to the world — the sense of something pent-up and about to burst. The anger and fear and the humane and inhumane reactions of characters both noble and base. A world about to explode seen through the experiences of one city with Adam as witness both to great events and the lives those events touch.</p>
<p>It’s the Deus Ex we all love — breaking into things and sneaking around and knocking people out and hacking all their secrets — but it feels like a more emotionally rich and <em>grown up</em> game than Deus Ex has managed before.</p>
<p><strong>One caveat</strong>: This is a <em>demanding</em> game. Playing on very high settings I got about 30-50 fps in most areas with my recent i7 and GTX 1070. I hear from my filthy Windows-using friends that it’s about the same on their stupid OS.</p>
<p><strong>Another caveat</strong>: The game got some poor reviews, especially community reviews, on release because of its <em>stupid</em> micro-transactions. That stuff is all either rectified or ignorable. I’ve played a <em>lot</em> of this game and never felt affected by it.</p>
<p>If you’ve got the PC to run it I’d <em>strongly</em> recommend Deus Ex: Mankind Divided, especially to fans of the series.</p>
<p>Deus Ex: Mankind Divided is available on <a href="http://store.steampowered.com/app/337000/Deus_Ex_Mankind_Divided/">Steam</a> and <a href="https://www.humblebundle.com/store/deus-ex-mankind-divided">Humble</a>.</p>
<div class="ytvid">
<iframe class="video" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/09vVF-Hvykg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen>
</iframe>
</div>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Forager</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/forager.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>I uninstalled Forager today.</p>
<p>Not because its bad but because its very good. It’s so good in fact that I found myself playing it when I didn’t want to. You see… It is well established that I like clickers a lot and use them as a sort of mood balancer. This works well for me. Load clicker, allow endorphins to arrive and work through bad/depressed mood. Its a good relationship that Clickers and I have. Forager however is a different beast and not something that fits into my Clicketty click symbiosis.</p>
<!--more-->
<p>Forager is a game about getting more and more resources, that allow you to unlock more resources. Its part clicker, part farming simulator, part resource management with a tiny dose of ARPG combat and Zelda like puzzles (very very small dose of that last one. But it IS in there)</p>
<p>Forager is not a clicker. It is a game that requires interaction. In fact, if you stand still for too long, a little slime will kill you. So you have to keep an eye out for the little boogers. Also, You will want to kill skeletons when they res-up, because they drop bones, also daemons, for horns. Oh, you may also want to plant more trees so they can be auto harvested by your mining poles. There’s also that stack of Royal steel you want to get to make some advanced materials.</p>
<p><a href="../images/forager_one.jpg"><img src="../images/forager_one.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>Forager is not a clicker. Forager is an engine for busy work. It’s a gloriously satisfying stream of numbers that trickle upwards. Each layer unlocking the next step in the everlasting rapture of satatisfaction (its like satisfaction but with numbers.) Actually, in that way, its a bit like Factorio, but Factorio allows you to literally automate the whole lot then go for a sandwich while you wait for resources to pool. Forager demands your attention all the time.</p>
<p>You can’t leave it. You constantly have to pick at its systems in meticulous ways. But the while time while you are doing this, there is literally no failure state. There is no way to end the game. If you do leave the game to its own devices while you hunt for food in the deepest reassesses of the kitchen that slime <em>will</em> get you. The game will then dump you back at the main menu and the numbers will stop going up. Once you return you have to click on the big load button and get back in moment before your demise. The point is though, that you <strong>have</strong> to pay attention. The whole time. If you don’t you are not only playing less efficiently but your progress halts entirely.</p>
<p>Clickers are good. Clickers allow you to receive satisfaction and progress. They scratch the itch (that basic desire for progression) while allowing you to be free to do other things (really, see <a href="http://ludiclinux.com/Clickers/">my post</a> about clickers if you want a more full explanation of this.) Forager doesn’t. Forager is less like an interactive screen saver and more like a sweat shop.</p>
<p><a href="../images/forager_two.jpg"><img src="../images/forager_two.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>Now all of this sounds negative, it is not supposed to be. Forager has found a way to add agency to the clicker formula. Essentially its a system for removing the ‘idle’ from the ‘idle game’ and for most gamers this would be great. For those of us who can literally spin our wheels for hundreds of hours in a ‘proper’ clicker, its a nightmare of attention whoring compulsion.</p>
<p>Today I uninstalled Forager because I could feel a little obsessive bell in my brain telling me I was going to play it until I had grown quite mad. Forager needed to be stopped.</p>
<p>I assume that the mandatory interactivity, the cute art style and the great sounds would make for an engaging game for the less obsessive. Forager is good. You should play it.</p>
<p>Here’s a video I made recently about Forager:</p>
<div class="ytvid">
<iframe class="video" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/DiQbfnWryv8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen>
</iframe>
</div>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Moonlighter</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/moonlighter.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>By all systems of measurement that I can point to, Moonlighter is a good game. It gets the much sought-after Mostly Positive on steam (both recent and all reviews), its MetaCritter score is 74 (Not top tier, but solid GOOD) and people tell me how great it is whenever it come up in conversation.</p>
<h3 id="so-what-is-it">So what is it?</h3>
<p>It can describe itself how it wants but its essentially a classically styled top-down action dungeon crawler that’s been Rogulite inspired (yes. that describes an ARPG, I know, but in this case that feels wrong.. by Odins staff why do people care so much about the exact genre a game falls into?)</p>
<p>The noteworthy feature of this one is that you don’t sell your loot to a merchant. You ARE the merchant (Insert mind blown meme here).</p>
<p>It’s published by 11 bit Studios and Developed by Digital Sun.</p>
<p>Steam will sell it to your for £15.29 British gold. I assume that’s like $22 American but I’m too lazy too check.</p>
<p>The basic loop is that you go to a dungeon at the edge of town, kill stuff, then go back to the store to ‘guess’ what people will pay for it. Make money for improvements and sponsor the township to get more shops to open (shops that help you make better stuff for your own shop)… and repeat. Its a solid idea and it seems like there maybe a reasonable amount of scope for fun.</p>
<h3 id="first-impressions">First Impressions</h3>
<p>My initial thoughts were really a stream of impressions, ones that were well documented as I streamed my fist load of the game.</p>
<p>Good solid pixel art - movement is slow - shop artwork is odd - menu is nice - grass pretty - really, That art is nice, but that shop is shitty.</p>
<p>Then I started to settle in and formed actual coherent thoughts.</p>
<p>The art is pretty dedicated to being <em>almost</em> top down. This means that all the walls in the dungeon are wider at the top/tilted away from camera, the people in the world however are at an angle so we can see their whole body. Not just the top of their head. It’s a striking trick that many a game has used over the years. Recently I commented how Swords of Ditto had done an excellent job implementing it.</p>
<p><a href="../images/moonlighter_shop.jpg"><img src="../images/moonlighter_shop.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>The main area of this game though, the one you see over and over. is the store — two connected rooms, the shop and the store room, that doubles up as a bedroom (where does the shop keeper piddle or shower? No… Don’t go off on a tangent, that’s not what the readers are here for… Are they? NO… Moving on.) The issue with this though is that both rooms are shown as this stylized ‘top down’ at the same time. HOW CAN THEY BOTH BE IN THE CENTRE OF THE FRAME? HOW?? - THEY CANT! While this is, in itself, nothing but a stylistic choice it really did bother me. I don’t even know why. It just constantly looks odd to me.</p>
<p>As the game went on, I began noticing other, tiny little artistic choices that poked my inner critic. The chunky controller labels on the UI, the lack of backdrop in the dungeon exit screen. Some colour palette overlap with the red stuff on the floor of the dungeon and the blood. The store also has a door that serves as a visual indicator of the ‘open’ status having an odd movement mechanic. Generally the art while being high quality is visually confusing at times. I realised after an hour or so that these choices all make sense in very low resolutions or on smaller screens. It’s like the art was tuned for the smaller screen of the Nintendo Switch rather than the massive screens we have on PCs.</p>
<p><a href="../images/moonlighter_red.jpg"><img src="../images/moonlighter_red.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>I was soon whisked away to the dungeon. Where I assume the monsters are kept. I was not disappointed. The combat while quite simple with buttons for attack and block, the addition of a dodge button makes it feel more technical than it actually is. I like this. Attack, dive out the way, block, back to attacking. Seems like it should be my kind of combat. If a little slow.</p>
<p>Once I was defeated in quite a scripted way I had to return to the shop to shop to see for myself how the retail aspect of this capitalist propaganda-piece would work. I actually did pay attention to the tutorial man. This is quite unusual for me.</p>
<p>Here’s how it works: You sell stuff by putting it on a table and giving it any price you fancy. When you open the shop customers will make little emoji faces at it. Grumpy for too pricey, happy for a good price. Ecstatic if it’s crazy cheap and offended/crying if its insultingly expensive. From this, with trial and error, you are supposed to get a good idea what is worth what. But, if you flood the market with stuff it will start to drop in value amd the market is ever changing. Sounds great - you also get a ledger that keeps track of each items history. All the tools you need!</p>
<h3 id="the-stuff-that-smelled-good">The stuff that smelled good</h3>
<p>The idea if fusing what you could consider management and dungeon battling is an interesting idea. While often games have fused genres together, I don’t recall a game ever trying to add non-killy systems to a game like this one. It’s an interesting idea.</p>
<p>The high detail artwork of the other shop-keepers is great. The potions lady for instance is vibrant and personality-filled in her store art. The larger monsters in the Dungeon look like they could be made into Plushy toys at any moment and the town has a wonderful green and brown palette that gives it a tired but hopeful look. I am a fan of this sort of art.</p>
<p>The concept of the shop and how it is stocked is fascinating and should make transactions personal. Letting something you fought for go for pennies should hurt. While that item you tripped over in the way in selling for a mountain of gold should make you feel richer than its sum.</p>
<h3 id="not-all-that-sparkles">Not all that sparkles</h3>
<p>The slight issues I have with the artwork can be ignored, its personal preference and its not something that I expect people to take me too seriously about, not when they have their own tastes to judge the stuff their eyes see. When it comes to the combat however, I think its a little more than opinion.</p>
<p><a href="../images/moonlighter_inventory.jpg"><img src="../images/moonlighter_inventory.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>The combat is slow to the point of infuriating at times. Many times I wanted to dodge an attack and the character responded <strong>just</strong> too late for it to matter. And even more times. I found myself attacking thin air because my character wasn’t lined up with the almost 2D enemy <em>quite</em> right. Now I’m sure with a little more practice I could compensate for this will learned skills but to me it is far away form feeling engaging, it feels like a chore to murder things. In a game about murdering things.</p>
<p>Once out of the dungeon you get the supposed thrill of pricing and marketing your wares before opening the shop to the public. This guess work and tweaking of prices to get best value for your goods is made even more tedious by the fact that you can only sell four items (some can stack) at any given time.</p>
<p>The constant fiddling with prices was solved for me when I just listed everything for 10 Gold each and put it out in varying quantities. If something didn’t sell after a few people looked at it swapped it out for something else. It’s like playing shelf stacker instead epic loot hunter. I must note though that even at its most tedious, its still technically well implemented. If I cared. There’s a whole games-worth of stats and details that would give me all the tools I needed to work out the best price…. <em>if I cared</em>.</p>
<h3 id="the-mash-paradox">The Mash paradox</h3>
<p>When a game wants to stand out from the crowed, one way is to mash two genres together. An obvious example is Hand of Fate that mashed brawler style combat with an RPG card game. Or how Total War games mash a sort of turn-based strategy Board Game with a real-time battle strategy simulation. The result of any game mash can be divisive. I, for instance, enjoy brawling <em>and</em> I love card games, so Hand of Fate is an easy sell for me. I like Board games but hate unit management so I bounce off about half of Total War’s total gameplay.</p>
<p><a href="../images/moonlighter_pool.jpg"><img src="../images/moonlighter_pool.jpg" /></a></p>
<p>In the case of Moonlighter, while messing with numbers and managing a shop should be fun, I just don’t enjoy this guess work mechanic at all. And while I love exploring a dungeon, this slow crawl isn’t for me. The Mash of the two things works even less. While I could see myself being in the shop management mood <em>or</em> being in the mood for a dungeon that’s slower than something like Enter the Gungeon, I can’t see myself being in the mood for both things on the same day.</p>
<h3 id="who-is-it-for">Who is it for?</h3>
<p>Well, here’s the problem, It seems to be <em>for</em> most people. Most people like the things that this game does. Most people are fascinated by the symbiosis of the shop and the adventure. Most people find the whole game a bit refreshing and like the overall slower pace.</p>
<p>You, the reader would most likely enjoy this game.</p>
<p><strong>I</strong> however did not. While I am quite able to see the polish and innovation of Moonlighter and I accept that it is the highest calibre of indie darling. I just fail to see the fun. I failed to enjoy this game on all levels. They can turn the combat up 20% faster, make the drops weapons only and let me just sell my loot to a merchant who can deal with it all for me and give me gold so I don’t have to give a shit about customers’ stupid emoji faces.</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 10</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-10.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 11</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-11.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 12</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-12.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 13</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-13.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 14</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-14.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 15</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-15.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 16</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-16.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 17</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-17.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 18</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-18.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 19</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-19.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 1</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-1.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 20</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-20.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 2</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-2.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 3</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-3.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 4</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-4.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 5</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-5.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 6</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-6.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 7</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-7.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 8</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-8.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Test Post 9</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/test-post-9.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 15:44:46 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>This is a test post</p>]]></description>
</item>



</channel>
</rss>
