<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

<channel>
<title>montti</title>
<description>montti's blog</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<link>https://montti.github.io/rss.xml</link>
<atom:link href="https://montti.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

<item>
<title>Literally just an oatmeal cookie recipe</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/literally-just-an-oatmeal-cookie-recipe.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 02:13:27 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>So it all started when I was a little boy… Just kidding, here’s the recipe.</p>
<h2 id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<p>For one oven-sized baking sheet of cookies:</p>
<ul>
<li>150 g of unsalted butter (less if you like dryer cookies, 100 g for example)</li>
<li>200 ml of sugar</li>
<li>400 ml of flour without baking soda</li>
<li>400 ml of non-instant rolled oats</li>
<li>1/2 tbsp of baking powder</li>
<li>1 tsp of salt</li>
<li>2 eggs</li>
<li>1 tbsp of vanilla essence (or more if you like vanilla a lot)</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mixing-baking">Mixing &amp; Baking</h2>
<ol type="1">
<li>Mix the dry ingredients well, including the oats.</li>
<li>Cut the butter in small chunks and place them over the mix.</li>
<li>Crack the eggs and add the vanilla essence.</li>
<li>Mix everything with your <strong>hands</strong> until homogenous, don’t use an electric mixer.</li>
<li>Take little chunks of cookie dough and plop them on the baking sheet, press a little on the top so they are vaguely disk shaped.</li>
<li>Bake at medium temp (I do not have a thermometer in my oven) and wait until the bottom of the cookies have a golden brown colour.</li>
<li>Let them cool down, they taste better at room temperature.</li>
</ol>
<p>Enjoy!</p>]]></description>
</item>


<item>
<title>So... you need to download NetBeans 8.2 in $CURRENT_YEAR</title>
<guid>https://montti.github.io/posts/so...-you-need-to-download-netbeans-8.2-in-$current_year.html</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 01:18:20 -0400</pubDate><description><![CDATA[<p>Maybe your institution curriculum is outdated and using this version is mandatory or maybe there’s some software environment that <em>just</em> doesn’t work with anything else, or you just like old software.</p>
<h2 id="first-things-first">First things first</h2>
<p>If you stumbled upon this page the official download links probably disappeared, again, but just in case please look around <a href="https://netbeans.apache.org/download/index.html">NetBeans webpage</a> or <a href="https://www.oracle.com/downloads/">Oracle’s</a>. The last working link was <a href="https://www.oracle.com/technetwork/java/javase/downloads/jdk-netbeans-jsp-3413139-esa.html">this one</a>. I insist on getting your downloads from an official site because even if I’m swell guy, downloading random .exe and .sh from the internet is a Bad Idea™.</p>
<p>If <em>that</em> didn’t work…</p>
<h2 id="archive-downloads">Archive Downloads</h2>
<p>I took the liberty of putting all the installation files in <a href="https://archive.org/details/jdk-8u111-nb-8_2">archive.org</a> and obviously I didn’t modify them, you just need to trust me ;) (don’t)</p>
<p>(The installation file is a co-bundle with the compatible Java version)</p>
<p>I REPEAT, USE ONLY IF THERE ISN’T AN ALTERNATIVE</p>
<p><a href="https://archive.org/download/jdk-8u111-nb-8_2/jdk-8u111-nb-8_2-linux-x64.sh">Linux</a></p>
<p><a href="https://archive.org/download/jdk-8u111-nb-8_2/jdk-8u111-nb-8_2-macosx-x64.dmg">MacOS</a></p>
<p><a href="https://archive.org/download/jdk-8u111-nb-8_2/jdk-8u111-nb-8_2-windows-x64.exe">Windows</a></p>
<p>And if you have a 32bit CPU from 2006 or something, first, bless your soul, second these are the links:</p>
<p><a href="https://archive.org/download/jdk-8u111-nb-8_2/jdk-8u111-nb-8_2-linux-i586.sh">Linux 32bit</a></p>
<p><a href="https://archive.org/download/jdk-8u111-nb-8_2/jdk-8u111-nb-8_2-windows-i586.exe">Windows 32bit</a></p>
<p>I hope that helped someone, cheers!</p>]]></description>
</item>



</channel>
</rss>
